All those who have been recreated
leave something of their past
in the Tri-Element Hall
Look. that's my teacher.
Your thoughts are really bothering me.
Just tell me what you want.
You get that feeling from my teacher's Moon Orb.
When the merge failed. you fell into the water.
The Moon Orb got rid of the fire on you.
My teacher said the Moon Orb would take me to her.
What Moon Orb? l'm not your teacher!
All weapons have their own spirit.
The Moon Orb was yours.
You may have changed.
but it can still recognize you
Take me for example.
l've tried but the Thunder Sword always evades me.
Heaven and Thunder have their own masters.
They won't go with anyone else.
Unless you erase their memory
in the Tri-Element Hall
you won't become its new master.
I've used the Heaven Sword to summon Thunder.
You must decide ...
whether you want to go in.
l'm the only clue to your past.
lf l go in.
Dawn will disappear forever from this world.
And you'll never know about the past.
You'll never be Dawn again.
Master Whitebrows!
Master!
He's not here!
No wonder we haven't seen him.
Moon Orb ...
Using it. l can get rid of the heat in your body.
How can l get my Moon Orb back?
Tell me!
Tell me how l can become your teacher again!
What can l do to save you?
Give me back the Moon Orb!
Give it back! l want to be your teacher again!
l suggest we reform Omei.
We can't go on without a chief.
l'm going to find brother Red.
and sister Enigma.
All of us together.
can ensure Omei's survival.
We'll fight to the end.
to the very last man!
For justice and for the Zu mountains!
Even if we lose.
we won't have failed our ancestors!
l'm going to find Red now.
Red!
lt's evil magic! Get back!
lt's very strong!
We can't hold out much longer.
Take shelter with other schools!
What's that? What's going on up there?
The magic's gone?
People up there have lost their powers?
l wonder if they know l'm ...
What. more?!
They're too strong. we can't hold them back.
Take my sword!
From now on. it's yours!
lt'll take you down the mountain.
Go!
Big brother
l've ... got you!
l've got you!
l've got the Heaven Sword!
l've destroyed Omei!
lnsomnia. you always say l'm a loser.
but now l've conquered Omei and the Zu mountains.
yet you're still inside that Blood Cave!
Phantom troopers. take her body away!
Red. spare no-one!
Raze the Golden Top
to the ground!
Where're you going with that sword?
Omei's finished. it's just a pile of rubble now.
What is this ghastly place?
Winner takes all. that's always how it is.
l'm a soldier.
l'll never allow myself be beaten!
l'm going back to kill the enemy!
Anyone trying to stop me is my enemy too!
Enemy?
You're just a rusty old sword.
you make me sick!
You're still not enlightened?
Not you too!
Our strength has been nullified.
lt'd be too late
even if you became enlightened
l wish l had inherited the Thunder Sword.
Let's go.
Right!
lf you're waiting for me to become enlightened.
what have you all been doing?
We've been waiting for you!
Thunder Sword!
Many students have lost their lives because of it!
Give it to me.
Give it to me!
l'll destroy it!
Give it here!
What? Are you scared you'd lose it?
lt won't remember. eh?
l'll help it remember!
lt may no longer be a rusty sword.
but it's still not much use.
if it had fought back sooner.
it may have helped.
Now it's too late.
You're on your own.
Can l go with you?
Fly!
This is high enough!
lt's the fire left by Grand Master.
Grand Master!
We've failed to protect Omei
the school's been destroyed.
Now there's only us left ...
Ying! You've extinguished Grand Master's fire!
Kneel! You must apologize!
No! An apology's not good enough!
Thrown him out!
But he has the Thunder Sword.
lt's just a sword!
You scoundrel! Bring Grand Master back!
Bring him back!
See the blue light in the sky?
That's a signal from Whitebrows.
He must have found what he wanted.
That's it! Let's get it!
Omei's survival depends on the 3 elements:
the power of the mind.
power of the universe and power of regeneration.
The power of regeneration is within you.
To have 3 forces combine as one.
Merge the 3 elements.
l've received the Ming Fire signal
from Whitebrows.
lt's time to launch a counter-attack.
But they've captured Enigma.
We must rescue her before we attack.
Your spirits will have to leave your bodies
to enter the Blood Cave.
lnsomnia will try everything he can
to find your physical beings and destroy them.
so your spirits will have no bodies to return to.
l suggest you leave your bodies on Point Nirvana.
Even if lnsomnia finds them.
we'll be able to hold him offer some time.
The school lives. we live ...
Look at you. so high up!
You have the whole world at your feet!
Good. eh?
Look. you're all shining in gold!
Soon the Blood River will
be looming high above Zu!
lnsomnia. come out now.
Today is your big day!
Your sword easily broke
through the enemy's defense
How does it feel to be victorious?
You'll soon get used to it.
l'll be with you. you won't be lonely.
lnsomnia!
What?
That's the Blood Clouds! Take cover!
Over to the canyon!
The Blood Clouds have totally covered
Green Castle.
Concentrate our powers on the Blood Cave.
we must rescue Enigma first!
The Blood Clouds have reached the Zu mountains.
myfriends are all there.
You want to go back and help them?
ln fighting the enemy.
You wouldn't abandon your men
on the battlefield. would you?
l understand. You go.
lf you lose this war.
it'll be disastrous for us too.
Take care!
There's a power of justice in the world.
l encountered it once.
unfortunately l didn't treasure it.
lf l could.
l'd like to rediscover that power.
At last. a chance to show my potential!
Here we meet again.
But you're no longer Red.
You're just a watch dog at Blood Cave!
Never mind the past!
l guess being the chief has made you humourless.
all that bureaucracy. eh?
Right now. l feel very differently to you.
Your heart is heavy.
But
l'm exhilarated.
l now realize what power means!
My power is constantly increasing.
And you.
you're like a mosquito to me.
if l speak a little louder l might blow you away
Enigma's down there.
What are you looking for?
Are you looking for her?
l'll levitate her. so you can have a better look.
That's just her physical being. her spirit ...
is right here!
Nonsense!
lf someone else's spirit is in you.
where is your own?
You want to know? Come in and find out!
Red!
Enigma!
Thunder Sword!
No! The Blood Cave will suck your sword away!
lt's got my sword!
Get your spirit inside Enigma's body
and rescue her
Good idea!
Stop bluffing. King Sky.
You won't kill me.
because l have Enigma's spirit inside me!
You don't have to remind me!
l won't kill you.
it's the witch inside you l want!
Ying. look after Enigma's spirit.
King Sky!
Teacher!
My destiny depends on your success.
Don't hesitate.
Go now!
My destiny depends on your success.
Don't hesitate. Go now!
Let's go!
Teacher ...
l'll worry about that when it happens.
l'll worry about that
when it happens.
We'll wait for you back at the school!
Teacher. finally l'm enlightened!
So. are you Ying. or are you Hollow?
You'd better call me Ying.
You can't use Heaven Sword in your present state.
We have to do it. we have to merge.
Right. Let's go back to Point Nirvana
to where my physical being is.
Recognize this? lt's the Sky Reflector.
The most powerful weapon in Omei.
Let's see what you can do!
The Blood Clouds!
We must prepare to merge soon!
The school lives. we live ...
The Buddha's Hands!
You bald ignoramuses!
Open your eyes.
this is what true power is.
The power is all mine!
Give me King Sky's body!
Look. your bodies!
Want to swallow me?
Quickly. we must help King Sky.
if his body is destroyed. he'll vanish forever.
King Sky. we've found your physical body.
Feeling bad. are you?
Because your body is now inside
lnsomnia's stomach.
Soon you'll become his 10.000th spirit.
you'll be his slave
forever!
Still you'll achieve one thing.
and that is. to live the rest of your life here!
You can't out with me.
You're not even close.
l lured you up to the Blood Cave.
so l could draw awayyour energy
everytime you hit me.
l've drawn off all the energy from your Ming Fire.
Try it if you don't believe me.
l'll give you what you want.
l'll stay here and die with you!
Master Transcendental ...
We can't get out. we've been surrounded!
lt's lnsomnia's spirit!
Thunder. take the master and go now!
Be careful!
Teacher. what now?
We must merge.
You must not hesitate
like Hollow did.
l won't this time! Let's merge now!
Heaven Strikes!
Thunder Fires!
Heaven and Thunder Swords represent yin and yang.
Yin and yang complement each other.
A swordsman must flow with the power
of his sword
and join as one.
Hesitancy and stubbornness
restricts the flow.
Thus. one will lose oneself.
and the merge will fail.
lf l'm not here when you come back.
The Moon Orb will find me.
Where are they?
They must have reached the speed of light
so we can't see them.
Over there!
The Blood Clouds
consist of 9.999 of my spirits.
l can be reborn with each spirit.
lf you want to kill me
you have to kill me 9.999 times.
But l'd only need to kill you once.
and you'll be gone forever!
9.999 times?
Even if there are 100.000. we'll kill them all!
Red!
Amnesia! You won't get away!
You must destroy me along with her.
if not.
she'll repossess my spirit!
Remember our agreement?
lf one of us is possessed by evil.
the other must not hesitate.
Kill me!
Kill you?
Why can't we join forces to fight that monster?
My physical being is not here.
it's in the Blood Cave.
My spirit is too weak to fly back.
Even if you don't kill me. l'll vanish.
There's still time.
to go back and find your body.
Though very old friends are we.
still we must part.
Kill me!
Good will triumph over evil.
Die!
Red! Help me!
Merge again!
His spirit is inside the Blood Clouds!
Separate them!
Right!
Without the Clouds. his spirit will be useless!
Separate him from the clouds!
Wait! King Sky is in his mouth!
lt's too close! Split up!
lt's the Ming Fire Sword!
l am inside your body.
lnsomnia. see where you can run now!
l've got Dawn's feelings back!
King Sky. l've found you at last.
After Heaven and Thunder failed in their merge.
Whitebrows used the sword's spirit
to recreate Ying.
Why don't you try to recreate Enigma?
Thunder Sword will help you find the Heaven Sword.
recreating Enigma is only a matter of time.
Omei is starting a new today.
You don't need me anymore.
l had promised my teacher
that l'd return to Kun Lun and rebuild the clan.
All the clans should respect
and support each other
Omei will rely on you from now on.
Heaven and Thunder have been born again.
you'll only merge successfully
if Heaven's new owner can be enlightened soon.
lt's no big deal flying around the mountains.
l'm not interested.
Don't worry. l was like her before.
l'll open up her mind soon!
l hope so.